Macbeth Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs, ca. 1880-ca. 1968, Series 8:; (Box 135-161; 12.1 linear feet)
  - Photographs of Artwork and Records of Paintings Sold, ca. 1900-1952, 8.3:
    - Bierstadt, Albert (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Bigelow, James (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Bingham, George Caleb (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Binoit, Peter (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Birch, Thomas (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Blackburn, Joseph (NMc74), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 142 (hol))
    - Blakelock, Ralph A. (NMc74), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 142 (hol))
    - Blashfield, Edwin H. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Blenner, Carle J. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Blommers (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Blum, Robert (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Blyth, David G. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Bohm, Max (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - Bostwick, Electra (NMc74), n.d., (3 folders) (Box 142 (hol))
    - Boughton, George H. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 142 (hol))
    - (Box 143 (hol))
    - Brackman, Robert (NMc74), n.d. (Box 143 (hol))
    - Braun, Maurice (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Brower, I. D. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Browere, Albertus, D. O. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Brown, George (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Brown, John George (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Brown, Mather (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Brown, Roy (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Browne, Belmore (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Bruestle, George W. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Brush, George de Forest (NMc74), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 143 (hol))
    - Bunker, Dennis (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Burchfield, Charles (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Bush, Joseph (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Butterworth, James E. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Butterworth, Thomas (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Cady, Harrison (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Campbell, Blendon (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Canade, Vincent (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Carlin (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Carlsen, Emil (NMc74), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 143 (hol))
    - Carlson, John F. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Carpenter, Horace T. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Carson, J. F. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Casilear, John W. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Cassatt, Mary (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Catlin, George (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Ceracchi, Giuseppe (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Chadwick (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Chamberlin, Mason (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Chapman, John Gadsby (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Chase, William Merritt (NMc74), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 143 (hol))
    - Chatterton, C. K. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Church, Frederic E. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Clonney, James (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Coates, E. C. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Cogniet, Leon (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 143 (hol))
    - Cole, Thomas (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Colman, Benjamin (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Connaway, Jay (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Copley, John Singleton (NMc74), n.d., (8 folders) (Box 144 (hol))
    - Corbino, Jon (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Corot, J. B. C. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Cosgrave, Esta (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Cotes, Francis (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Crane, Bruce (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Cropsey, Jasper (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Culver, Charles (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Currier, Frank (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Curry, John S. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Cushing, Lily (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Custer, Bernadine (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Daingerfield, Elliott (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Darley, Felix O. C. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 144 (hol))
    - Davies, Arthur B. (NMc74), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (13 folders) (Box 145 (hol))
    - Davis, Charles H. (NMc75), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 145 (hol))
    - Day, Horace (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 145 (hol))
    - De Martini, Joseph (NMc75), n.d., (5 folders) (Box 145 (hol))
    - Dearth, Henry Golden (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Deas, Charles (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Decker, Joseph (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Demuth, Charles (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Derujinsky, Gleb (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Despiau, C. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Dessar, Louis Paul (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Dewing, Maria Oakey (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Dewing, Thomas W. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Dickinson, Preston (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Dixon, Maynard, ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Dougherty, Paul (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Doughty, Thomas (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Duche, Thomas Spencer (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Dummer, Jeremiah (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Dunlap, William (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Durand, Asher B. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Durand, John (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Durrie, George H. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Duveneck, Frank (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Eakins, Thomas (NMc75), n.d., (3 folders) (Box 146 (hol))
    - Earl, James (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Earl, Ralph (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Eastman, Seth (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Eaton, Charles (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Edmunds, Francis (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 146 (hol))
    - Edwin, David (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Ehninger, John W. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Eicholtz, Jacob (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Eilshemius, Louis (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Elliott, Charles Loring (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Emmons, Nathaniel (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Epstein, Jacob (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Faden, William (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Feke, Robert (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Ferneley, John (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Field, Robert (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Finck, Furman Joseph (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Flagg, George (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Flanagan, John (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Forrest, John (Ian) B. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Foster, Ben (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Foster, Gerald (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Fraser, Charles (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Frieseke, Frederick Carl (NMc75), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 147 (hol))
    - Frothingham, James (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Fuller, George (NMc75), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 147 (hol))
    - Fulton, Robert (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gaertner, Carl (NMc75), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gainsborough, Thomas (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Garber, Daniel (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gasser, Henry (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gay, Edward (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gifford, Sanford (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gignoux, Regis (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gill, Paul (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Glackens, William J. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gleitsmann, Raphael (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Greene, Stephen (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Greenwood, John (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Grimm, William (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Groll, Albert (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gross, Herman (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Gustin, Paul Morgan (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Hall, Carl (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Harding, Chester (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Harding, F. L. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Harnett, William (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Hart, George "Pop" (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Hart, James M. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Hart, William W. (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 147 (hol))
    - Hartley, Marsden (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Harvey, George (NMc75), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Hassam, Childe (NMc75/Nmc76), n.d., (4 folders) (Box 148 (hol))
    - Havell, Robert (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Hawthorne, Charles Webster (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Heade, Martin Johnson (NMc76), n.d., (2 folders) (Box 148 (hol))
    - Healy, Arthur (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Healy, George P. A. (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Hedley, Joseph (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Helder, Z. Vanessa (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Helling, I. Arthur (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 148 (hol))
    - Henri, Robert (NMc76), n.d., (3 folders) (Box 149 (hol))
    - Henry, E. L. (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Hesselius, John (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Heyligers, Helen (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Hibbard, Aldro T. (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Hicks, Edward (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Hicks, Thomas (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Higgins, Eugene (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Hinckley, Thomas H. (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Hofmann, Knickerbocker & Co. (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Holt, Henry (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 149 (hol))
    - Homer, Winslow, Book One (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (3 folders) (Box 149 (hol))
    - Homer, Winslow, Book Two, A-L (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (9 folders) (Box 150 (hol))
    - Homer, Winslow, Book Two, M-Z (NMc76), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (8 folders) (Box 151 (hol))
    - Homer, Winslow, Book Three (NMc76/NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (8 folders) (Box 152 (hol))
    - Homer, Winslow, Book Four (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Homer, Winslow (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (4 folders) (Box 153 (hol))
    - Hope, Capt. James (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Hopper, Edward (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Howell, Felicie Waldo (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Howorth, George (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Huffington, John (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Hunt, William M. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Huntington, Daniel (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Hurd, Peter (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Inman, Henry (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 153 (hol))
    - Inness, George (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (2 folders) (Box 154 (hol))
    - Irvine, Wilson (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - James, Alexander (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Janney, Francis (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Jarvis, J. W. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - John, Augustus (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Johnson, David (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Johnson, Eastman (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Johnson, John (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Johnson, Theodore (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Jouett, Matthew H. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Kane, John (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Kellogg, E. B. and E. C. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Kensett, John F. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Kent, Rockwell (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Knapp, George K. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Koch, John (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Kopman, Benjamin (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Kosa, Emil J. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Kuehne, Max (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Kuhn, Walt (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - La Farge, John (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Lahey, Richard (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Lamar, Julian (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Laning, Edward (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Lavalle, John (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Lawless, Carl (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Lawrence, A. A. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Lawson, Ernest (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 154 (hol))
    - Le Paon, J. B. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lechay, James (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Leney, William S. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lever, Hayley (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lewis (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lewis & Brown (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lewis & Goodwin (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lie, Jonas (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lintott, E. Barnard (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lithographs (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lowell, F. E. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Luce, Molly (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lucioni, Luigi (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Luks, George (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Lungren, Fernand (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Maillol, Aristide (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Malbone, Edward G. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Manship, Paul (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Maril, Herman (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Marin, John (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Marsh, Reginald (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Martin, Homer Dodge (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Martin, John B. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Mason, Roy (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Mattern, Karl (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Matteson, Tompkins H. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Maurer, Louis (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - McEntee, Jervis (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - McFee, Henry L. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - McNulty, William C. (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Melchers, Gari (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Meltzer, Arthur (NMc77), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Mennetti, A. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Metcalf, Eliab (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Metcalf, Willard L. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Meyer, Felicia (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Meyer, Herbert (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 155 (hol))
    - Miller, J. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Miller, Kenneth H. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Miller, Richard E. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Millet, J. F. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Mitchell, Bruce (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Moore, Nelson A. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Moran, Edward (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Moran, Thomas (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (2 folders) (Box 156 (hol))
    - Mount, Shepard A. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Mount, William S. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Murphy, H. Dudley (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Murphy, John Francis (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Myers, Jerome (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Neagle, John (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Netscher, C. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Nettleton, Walter (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Newman, Robert L. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Newton, Gilbert Stuart (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Nichols, Dale (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Nichols, Henry H. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Nichols, Spencer B. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Noble, John (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - O'Donovan, William R. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Olinsky, Ivan (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Olson, Olaf (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Otis, Bass (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Palmer, Walter (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Paradise, John (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Parcell, Malcolm (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Paton, Herbert (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Peale, Charles Willson (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Peale, Harriet C. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Peale, James (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Peale, Rembrandt (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Peale, Rubens (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Pease, Harry E. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Pelham, Peter (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Pennell, Joseph (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Perry, Enoch Wood (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Petticolas, Edward F. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Pierce, Waldo (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Phillips, Robert (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 156 (hol))
    - Platt, Charles A. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Pleissner, Ogden (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Polk, Charles Peale (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Poor, Henry Varnum (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Postels, A. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Pratt, Matthew (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Prendergast, Charles E. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Prendergast, Maurice (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Presser, Josef (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Prestopino, Gregorio (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Pringle, James (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Pushman, Hovsep (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Quidor, John (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Raeburn, Henry (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Rand, Ellen Emmet (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Ranney, William (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Rawson, Albert L. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Redfield, Edward W. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Redon, Odilon (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Reid, Robert (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Reindel, Edna (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Remington, Frederick (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Reynolds, Joshua (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Richardson, Constance C. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Ritman, Louis (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Ritschel, William T. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Robinson, Theodore (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Romney, George (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Ross, Harry L. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Ross, Sanford (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Rousseau, Theodore (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Rowlandson, Thomas (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Ruggles, Carl (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Russell, Charles M. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - Ryder, Albert Pinkham (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (2 folders) (Box 157 (hol))
    - Ryder, Chauncey F. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 157 (hol))
    - St. Memin, Charles (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sample, Paul (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Santo, Patsy (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sargent, Henry (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sargent, John S. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sartain, William (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Savage, Edward (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Schucker, Charles (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Schweitzer, Gertrude (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sears, Taber (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Seyffert, Leopold (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sharples, James (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Shean, Charles W. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Shinn, Everett (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sloan, John (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Smibert, John (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (3 folders) (Box 158 (hol))
    - Smith Brothers (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sonntag, William L. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sorine (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Soyer, Moses (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Soyer, Raphael (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Speicher, Eugene (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sprinchorn, Carl (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sterne, Maurice (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Sterner, Albert (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Stettheimer, Florine (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Stevens, Stanford (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Story, William W. (NMc78), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Stuart, Gilbert (NMc78/NMc79), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (9 folders) (Box 158 (hol))
    - Stuart, Jane (NMc79), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 158 (hol))
    - Stumpfeig, Walter (NMc79), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 159 (hol))
    - Sully, Thomas (NMc79), ca. 1910-ca. 1952, (3 folders) (Box 159 (hol))
    - Symons, Gardner (NMc79), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 159 (hol))
    - Tack, Augustus Vincent (NMc79), ca. 1910-ca. 1952 (Box 159 (hol))